“Hey now, Cosette. Don’t be rude to Lady Celia. I’m terribly sorry about her, Lady Celia,” Natalie said immediately.

“I’ll also have a strong word with her later,” Aria added, making Cosette stiffen with a groan.

“There’s no need for that. Today is a day for social exchange and there’s no need to be so formal. I’m glad to have the chance to talk to the people Aria normally works with. You’re surrounded by some wonderful colleagues, Aria,” Celia giggled, looking at Aria.

“Yes. It’s all thanks to you.” Aria shrugged as if in exasperation and then nodded, but her expression softened faintly.

“You were classmates with Lady Celia, right?” Natalie asked.

“Yes, that’s right,” Aria replied.

“Aria’s always as strict as a demon from hell, but was she this strong in school too?” Cosette asked Celia next.

“There was no one who could beat Aria in swordsmanship. She was better than all the boys too. She was evenly matched against Haruto as well—you really are incredibly strong, Aria.”

“Sir Haruto was focused on defending until the very end, so I wouldn’t call us evenly matched...”

“Really? To be honest, I don’t know much about swords...”

“I was attacking rather seriously, but he parried everything easily. I’m not sure I would have a chance of winning if we fought until the end... At the very least, I wasn’t able to see all of Sir Haruto’s abilities in that match.” Aria looked back on her fight with Rio in contemplation.

“Has Sir Haruto ever struggled with a fight until now?” Cosette asked Celia.

“Hmm, I wonder. It’s hard to measure his true strength, so I can’t imagine him losing... He’s just as strong as Aishia, I think,” Celia answered, looking over at where Aishia was seated with Miharu and Liselotte.

“That’s true. I fought her briefly during the latter half of the lesson, but she was very strong. Lady Sara and Lady Alma too...” Natalie said.

The latter half of the lesson had been a mock battle focused on Rio’s teachings, so Aishia, Sara, and Alma had assisted in conducting the matches, but Aishia had gone undefeated. Only Aria was able to fight until a tie was called. (Sara and Alma lost to Aria, but they won against every other participant.)

“Her strength was one thing, but isn’t Aishia’s cuteness unmatched? When I saw her face close up, I was shocked at how refined it was... Her skin’s so white as well. I lost so quickly while I was staring out of envy.” Cosette let out a dreamy sigh in reverence.

“At least fight properly...” Natalie muttered tiredly under her breath.

“Ah ha ha... Her appearance can even captivate people of the same sex. I’ve gotten used to it while living with her, but sometimes I’m reminded of her beauty and lose confidence in myself,” Celia said listlessly.

“Umm, your beauty is enough to make other women jealous as well, no?” Natalie protested to Celia.

“Indeed. If you’re the same age as Aria, that makes you the same age as us—yet you still look like you’re in your teens. You’re like a fairy, a sweet young girl,” Cosette added.

“I’m often told I have a baby face...” Celia hung her head in disappointment.

“What’s wrong with that? Maintaining your youth and beauty is your ultimate duty as a lady, no? Your appearance is a powerful weapon anyone would envy, Lady Celia. And I believe your senses have been numbed by all the beautiful girls around Sir Haruto, because you’re definitely included as one of them.”

“Th-Thank you very much...” Celia said hesitantly, pressured by Cosette.

“It looks like you’re all having fun.”

Just then, Vanessa came up to them. Beside her was the captain of Charlotte’s guards, Louise.

“Good day to you, Vanessa. I watched a part of your training earlier—I’m glad to see you’re better and back on your feet,” Celia, the one most familiar with Vanessa, said.

“Yes, I’m in my best condition thanks to Sir Amakawa. But that aside... Are the two of you acquainted with each other?” Vanessa looked between Celia and Aria.

“...Yes, we were classmates back at the Royal Academy.” Celia glanced at Aria to check she was allowed to reply before giving her answer.

“I see... That means your grade was a particularly impressive one, since you have a magic genius and a sword genius in the same year.”

“Celia has achieved great success as a sorcerer, but you’re overevaluating me. I dropped out of the academy without ever graduating.”

“No, it’s vexing, but there’s no doubt you were the most skilled out of all the participants today. Our kingdom suffered an immeasurable loss by letting you go so easily. The only consolation is that you went to our alliance kingdom, Galarc...”

“It’s an honor to be told that, but it’s not that big of a deal.” Aria shook her head respectfully.

“The same applies for Sir Amakawa, but it seems true geniuses are humble about themselves. The attendants of Duke Cretia’s daughter are all talented, but the head attendant is on another level—one of the leading swordmasters in the kingdom, for sure. That’s the word in the castle, and I consider the rumors to be true,” Louise said, joining in on the conversation by praising Aria.

“It’s an honor...”

“I’d love to invite someone as skilled as you into the royal guards, but...”

“I’m sorry, I have no intention of serving anyone other than Lady Liselotte.”

“What wonderful loyalty.”

“Aria is both an attendant and a knight...”

Louise gave an approving smile at Aria’s immediate reply, while Vanessa complimented her in admiration, though she seemed a little conflicted about it.

“At any rate, I’m sure we’ll be seeing more of each other at the training sessions. Let’s get along well. As leaders of our own groups, it’d be nice to be close to each other.”

“Of course, it’d be my pleasure.” Aria accepted the hand Vanessa offered to shake.

“Sir Amakawa said he wasn’t confident in his abilities as an instructor, but it’s a rare opportunity to receive coaching from someone of his strength. The participants are all skilled as well. It’ll be a wonderful training experience. Let’s all strengthen our abilities together.”

“Indeed. We should be grateful to Her Highness for providing the opportunity, and to Sir Amakawa for agreeing to teach us.” Louise also shook hands with Aria.

“We were even treated to a wonderful bath experience and a delicious meal afterwards. I would have liked to thank Sir Amakawa for it, but...”

“Unfortunately, it seems like he’s left the room for the moment. I’m sure he’ll show up again later, so please tell him then,” Celia said to Vanessa, who was looking around in search of Rio.

“Right. My subordinates also wanted to speak to him. They’ll be disappointed,” Vanessa said with a wry smile.

“Mine too.” Louise echoed her sentiment with a sigh.

“Was there something they wished to discuss?” Celia asked, tilting her head.

“Our work doesn’t provide much opportunity to meet new people. To be honest, everyone’s starved,” Vanessa explained.

Women were normally used as guards for female royalty, but the constant changing of guards was looked down upon, which made the job rather difficult to quit. Many noblemen disliked how their resignation was restricted, so female knights were known for missing their prime marriage age, which only further spurred the lack of female knights for protecting female royalty.

“The situation is the same in every kingdom, it seems.”

“It’s similar for attendants as well.”

Louise and Aria spoke with self-deprecating smiles. Beside them, Cosette and Natalie nodded firmly in agreement.

“Ah ha ha...” Celia laughed awkwardly in understanding.

Interlude: A Conversation between Ruler and Saint

In the Proxia Castle, at the arena where Rio once crossed swords with Nidoll while infiltrating in search of Lucius’s whereabouts...

There was a short boy with a halberd and a skinny man. The boy was Kikuchi Renji, who had worked as an adventurer after he was summoned into this world up until a short while ago. The skinny man was none other than the Proxia Empire’s ambassador, Reiss.

Renji wielded his Divine Arms—the halberd—while running around the arena field.

“Ha!”

Renji was currently in the middle of combat training. Reiss had positioned himself in the spectator seats at a place with a good view, creating countless spheres of light and firing them at Renji from afar.

“Haaagh!”

Renji ran through the encircling net of light, occasionally swinging his halberd to mow down those who approached too close.

Hmm... He’s able to move well now. His assessment of the situation has become more accurate as well.

Reiss thought in praise of Renji’s growth while controlling the rain of light. Just then—

“Sir Vulfe.”

A knight ran over to Reiss. He seemed to be in a hurry, as he was panting slightly. Incidentally, “Vulfe” was Reiss’s family name when he was working as the Proxia Empire’s ambassador.

“What is it?”

“The emperor has summoned you. Please make your way to the audience hall immediately.”

“The audience hall...” Reiss placed a hand over his mouth in thought.

I wasn’t given any advance warning, so it must be an unexpected visitor. Someone he’s willing to meet when he has no interest in government affairs... Either a very important guest, or a rare and unexpected one.

Reiss guessed that much in an instant and smiled. It was most likely that Nidoll wanted Reiss present for that meeting.

“I understand. I shall head there immediately. Please inform Renji that he is to train by himself for now.”

With those words, Reiss ceased casting the countless light orbs and left.

What...? Is training over for today? I was finally getting warmed up too...

Surprised by the sudden end of the attacks, Renji looked up from the field and watched Reiss leave with a disappointed expression.

◇　◇　◇

Ten minutes later, Reiss had arrived at the audience hall of the Proxia Castle. At the farthest end of the room, facing the door, was the platform where Emperor Nidoll Proxia sat on the throne, looking down on the visitor in the hall below the steps.

There were only two people in the room other than Reiss. Reiss hid in a position that couldn’t be seen by the visitor to watch the scene.

Well, this is a rather rare guest. Reiss stared at the visitor and twisted his mouth in a crooked beam. It was a black-haired woman in a habit-styled dress. Normally, one wouldn’t be allowed to raise their head before Nidoll without permission, but...

“What kind of nation can’t even offer a guest a chair? How boorish this so-called Proxia Empire must be.”

The woman showed no particular reverence towards Nidoll and strongly expressed her displeasure instead. Her tone was calm and polite, but the content of her words was awfully provocative. A textbook example of superficial courtesy.

“Bwa ha ha, the boor that barged in for an audience with no appointment is preaching manners? What absurdity.” Nidoll didn’t appear to be bothered by the woman’s words and attitude, laughing it off heartily.

He’s enjoying himself.

Having known him for a long time, Reiss could trace Nidoll’s thoughts somewhat well. Nidoll normally lamented the boredom of staying inside the castle all the time, so he probably found the sudden appearance of an aggressive conversation partner amusing.

“Since you accepted a sudden meeting with a stranger, I had high hopes the Proxia Emperor would be a broad-minded person... I guess I was wrong. You’re just a small fry who can’t even look at your conversation partner from the same eye level,” the woman said sadly, intentionally provoking Nidoll.

“You’re not completely unknown to me. You’re the famous saint, aren’t you?” Nidoll smiled with the calmness of an emperor, guessing at her identity without falling for her provocations. Indeed, the woman was Saint Erica.

“Oh, you’ve heard of me?” Erica’s eyes widened in surprise.

“I received word that one of my remote vassal states was overthrown and a new nation established.”

“Word sure reached you fast.”

“It was an interesting change in the boring state of international politics. It left an impression on me. What is your goal? Visiting the ruler of the suzerain state to the nation you overthrew with a revolution, all by yourself. Quite the whimsical move, really,” Nidoll said with a chuckle.

“I merely came to observe this nation and meet its ruler,” Erica replied, boldly yet calmly.

“Observe what, exactly?”

“The lifestyle of the people in this nation and whether they’re being oppressed by the ruler—which would be you.”

“Ha ha, ha ha ha!”

“What’s so funny?”

“A suspicious woman claiming to be the saint suddenly arrives and declares she’s judging whether the people are being oppressed to the emperor himself. Who wouldn’t laugh at that? It certainly isn’t the work of someone sane. However...” Nidoll stared at Erica, suppressing his laughter.

“I’m perfectly sane, though.” Erica cocked her head curiously.

“Very well... So how did this nation appear in your saint’s eyes?”

“I’m not looking at the nation, but the people living within it. In other words, the citizens and their ruler.”

“I consider that to be the same thing. And?”

“Allow me to get straight to the point. Abdicate the throne and hand the nation to the people immediately. That will lead to the salvation of the people.” Erica glared coldly at Nidoll, who reclined in his throne arrogantly.

“I cannot see how dragging the ruler from his throne will lead to salvation for the people. What if I refuse?”

“Punitive justice,” Erica declared without hesitation.

“Oh? Would you like to try that right here and now?” Nidoll grinned in challenge, welcoming a fight. He gripped the hilt of the broadsword he carried everywhere with him, even the audience hall. However...

“No, now is not the right time. There’s no revolution without the will of the people. The people of this nation must first learn.” Erica shook her head calmly.

“Not the right time, you say? After making your way to the very heart of the empire and declaring war, do you expect to walk away freely?” Nidoll gestured to his sword, threatening to stand up and draw it at any moment.

“In that case, I have no choice.”

Erica didn’t falter. A beautiful khakkhara-like mace appeared out of seemingly nowhere, which she grasped in her hand. She stared back at Nidoll flatly, as though she thought nothing of him—like he wasn’t even worth her notice—and assumed a fighting stance.

The air between the two of them was on the verge of erupting, when Nidoll suddenly spoke up.

“I believed you a foolish woman drunk on power beyond your means, but it seems you’re no mere jester. You’re more of a wicked witch.” After staring at Erica’s face in suspicion, Nidoll lowered his hand from his sword hilt. He deemed Erica a witch, not a saint.

“Heh. Heh heh heh. Calling a saint a witch? What harsh words.”

It was at this moment that Erica showed a human-like emotion for the first time. Her mouth twisted in an ecstatic grin.